thaisale.co.th 2013-12-10

# Thaisale.co.th - Privacy

OZSALE.COM.AU, referred to below as Ozsale, is an online retailer of consumer goods.

Ozsale values our relationship with you and the other users of this website. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information that we may collect when you use the Web Site. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our contact us page.

## OZSALE's Commitment to Online Security

Your personal information is treated with the greatest of care. Sensitive payment information such as credit card details are NEVER stored on the Internet with our system.

## How Your Information May Be Shared

We never sell or rent your personal information. OZSALE may release personal information under the following circumstances:

  * Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;
  * Where our records indicate a company or an individual may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
  * To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

## Invite a friend

Ozsale provides facilities throughout the site to refer friends to Ozsale. You may not use the "Invite a friend" service or other email forwarding services that we offer to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our privacy policy or Terms and Conditions. We do not permanently store, sell, or rent these email messages or the email addresses.

## Membership Registration

Our site's registration form requires you to provide us contact information and may also require demographic information. We may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

## Passwords

You are responsible for all actions taken with your user name, email address and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your Ozsale password to any third parties. If you choose to share your user name, email address and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with this information and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy.

## Security

OZSALE PTY LIMITED uses NAB Transact to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card and charge card transactions. Confidential information including card details are encrypted  using industry standard SSL 128-bit encryption technology.

Our payment page is also fully PCI DSS compliant please visit <https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/tech/> for more information.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use our Web site. We use cookies to improve the member experience. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major Web sites.

Ozsale mostly uses "session" cookies, which are removed from your computer once you leave Ozsale. These are used so our service can remember that you have logged in already and prevent you doing so more frequently. The technology we use (Microsoft .NET), requires the use of session cookies. Session cookies expire and are deleted after 30 minutes of no activity on Ozsale.

Ozsale also uses persistent cookies to personalise the user experience, to help protect our members and to provide us with research information (such as how often members visit Ozsale each month). Persistent cookies allow us to track users on Ozsale and help us identify users abusing the Ozsale service.

## Membership Removal

If you wish to be removed from our database for any reason, simply send us an email requesting to be removed via our contact us page.

## Updates to our information practices

Ozsale reserves the right to add to, delete or change these terms because of frequent changes in Internet technology and applicable law. As such, you should check this privacy policy from time to time for such changes.
